icarly.ca 2009-07-10

# iCarly.com

At YTV.com, we understand and appreciate the concerns that parents and families may have with regard to information gathered about Site users surfing our website, or on any other website.

The YTV website gathers different kinds of information from its visitors.

A user can enter a YTV contest through our website YTV.com. If a user is under the age of 13 we require parental consent prior to the submission of a user's personal information. On the online entry form, we ask for personal information such as your name and address. This personal information is collected, used and/or disclosed solely for the purpose of awarding contest prizes, tracking compliance with the official rules and regulations and for internal feedback purposes. YTV only uses and discloses a contest winner's name and photograph after receiving prior written consent from the winner (or their parent/guardian) and the appropriate release forms are fully completed by a parent/guardian and returned to YTV.

YTV uses a third party company (YTV's contest fulfillment house) to draw winners names, contact winners and send prizing to you. The personal information collected by this company is solely for the purpose of the contest fulfillment, and this company is contractually obligated to maintain the private and/or confidential nature of the collected information.

All contest and stored information, including personal information, received from our visitors remains the exclusive property of YTV and is not sold or distributed. Contest entry names and information are seen only by YTV and YTV's contest fulfillment house. Such information is stored in a secure location and only accessible for as long as is necessary to fulfill the purposes for which it is collected, and it is destroyed, in a manner which ensures that the private and/or confidential nature of the information is preserved, typically within Sixty (60) days after those purposes have been fulfilled.

Each YTV employee signs confidentiality agreements upon employment with the company, and is trained to carry out and implement YTV's Privacy Policy.

Occasionally, YTV.com users will have the opportunity to submit ideas or content such as videos for inclusion on some shows airing on YTV. At this time, the producers of these shows will also ask the users to include a contact number, email or address. Only those who produce the show in question will have access to the contact information and it will not be passed on to a third party. People who submit ideas or content may be contacted if the show's producers decide to use their submissions.

Occasionally visitors are invited to voluntarily answer polls or survey questions that may be used in conjunction with sponsors/business partners. Be assured that in these poll and survey situations, only general (not personal) information such as gender, age and postal code is collected. The information collected ensures that visitors remain anonymous.

YTV tracks the number of visits to our Site. For example, we count how many times people access the YTV Guide page on the Site. All information gathered in this way is generic, and we do not track any individual users from this, but only calculate how many visits have taken place.

Cookie technology is used on our Site to maximize the Site experience. For example, we use cookies to keep track of a user's time zone information which allows us to customize our schedule and give accurate show times. We also use cookies to keep track of a user's progress through a game we may have on our Site. No personal information is gathered from these cookies.

When a user sends an email message to YTV through the website, two pieces of information are automatically stamped on the message. These are the time that the message was sent, and the IP address it was sent from. This is a precautionary measure against any potentially threatening messages being sent to YTV, its staff, or the public. This information is only used in those extreme cases where we feel someone's safety may be at risk.

YTV.com is a Site for kids. Therefore, there are certain laws that we are required to follow. One of the rules is that users under the age of 16 require parental consent prior to providing any personal information. However, there are other important privacy measures we take such as never asking for more personal info than what we deem necessary - and storing any info we do collect in a secure database only accessible by the YTV.com staff. We take extra steps to prevent members from disclosing their personal info on our Site by monitoring the interactive features and actively enforcing our rules.

Any personal identifiable info collected from our members is for YTV.com purposes only (e.g. Membership verification, contest fulfillment, etc.) We will never sell or give any of this information to third parties. Sometimes we may share aggregated info collected from our Polls, however specific Members are never identified.

Please keep in mind that this Privacy Policy applies to YTV.com only. Occasionally, we may have links to other Sites, including those of sponsors and partners. And although we do our best to ensure that these third parties share our views about privacy protection and safety, we don't have control over how they collect and use personal information from visitors. That's why always a good idea to check out a Site's privacy policy - even if you've linked to it from YTV.com.

We review this policy regularly and will update it (and other sections of our website) whenever necessary. If there are ever changes made to the way we collect or use personal information, we will always inform our Members.

With YTV.com Membership, users will have the option to receive email Newsletters from YTV.com. The Newsletter will be sent out periodically and provide program updates, information on special events, new contests, and YTV host messages. This Newsletter can be cancelled at any time by following the simple steps outlined at the bottom of the Newsletter.

The web is a great place to hang out, to find out stuff, and to share comments and ideas with people who are into the same kind of stuff you are.

But the net isn't always a safe place - so we've put together some tips for you to read that will help you handle situations if they come up.

First thing is don't give out personal information without asking your parents. Personal information can mean:

Your name 

Your address 

Your phone number 

Your mom or dad's name 

The name of your school 

Your teacher or your friend's names 

Secondly, if you run into something on the internet that makes you uncomfortable - whether it's on the web or it's sent to you - tell your mom or dad, or an adult you can talk to, and get them to deal with it. Never agree to meet anyone you have "met" online.

Never send your picture over the internet without checking with your parents or another adult. Don't answer mean messages, or rude ones, or messages asking for personal information. If you do get a message like that - tell your parents right away, so they can help you deal with it. Make sure you obey the rules that your parents have set out for you. Make up a cool nickname for when you join a chat or a game online. Never tell anyone your real name or your password. Get your parents to read the safety for parent's tips.

The web is a great place for kids to hang out and learn about topics that are of interest to them. However, there are areas on the internet that are not appropriate for children.

The guidelines we have drawn up are a starting point for parents of children who surf. The most important thing is to be aware of what your children are doing online. This may mean surfing with your children, or talking to them about the Sites that they like or that they have recently discovered on the web.

Make surfing a family activity, particularly with young children.

Set ground rules, so each person knows what is expected of them. For example, you could go through the safety tips together so everyone understands the whats and the whys.

There are software programs that allow parents to block certain websites from their kids. Some programs are more flexible than others, so you may want to shop around to find one that you're comfortable with.

Any questions, comments or requests concerning the YTV Privacy Policy can be directed to G.Remy, Privacy Officer at interactive@corusent.com.
At YTV.com, we understand and appreciate the concerns that parents and families may have with regard to information gathered about Site users surfing our website, or on any other website.

The YTV website gathers different kinds of information from its visitors.

A user can enter a YTV contest through our website YTV.com. If a user is under the age of 13 we require parental consent prior to the submission of a user's personal information. On the online entry form, we ask for personal information such as your name and address. This personal information is collected, used and/or disclosed solely for the purpose of awarding contest prizes, tracking compliance with the official rules and regulations and for internal feedback purposes. YTV only uses and discloses a contest winner's name and photograph after receiving prior written consent from the winner (or their parent/guardian) and the appropriate release forms are fully completed by a parent/guardian and returned to YTV.

YTV uses a third party company (YTV's contest fulfillment house) to draw winners names, contact winners and send prizing to you. The personal information collected by this company is solely for the purpose of the contest fulfillment, and this company is contractually obligated to maintain the private and/or confidential nature of the collected information.

All contest and stored information, including personal information, received from our visitors remains the exclusive property of YTV and is not sold or distributed. Contest entry names and information are seen only by YTV and YTV's contest fulfillment house. Such information is stored in a secure location and only accessible for as long as is necessary to fulfill the purposes for which it is collected, and it is destroyed, in a manner which ensures that the private and/or confidential nature of the information is preserved, typically within Sixty (60) days after those purposes have been fulfilled.

Each YTV employee signs confidentiality agreements upon employment with the company, and is trained to carry out and implement YTV's Privacy Policy.

Occasionally, YTV.com users will have the opportunity to submit ideas or content such as videos for inclusion on some shows airing on YTV. At this time, the producers of these shows will also ask the users to include a contact number, email or address. Only those who produce the show in question will have access to the contact information and it will not be passed on to a third party. People who submit ideas or content may be contacted if the show's producers decide to use their submissions.

Occasionally visitors are invited to voluntarily answer polls or survey questions that may be used in conjunction with sponsors/business partners. Be assured that in these poll and survey situations, only general (not personal) information such as gender, age and postal code is collected. The information collected ensures that visitors remain anonymous.

YTV tracks the number of visits to our Site. For example, we count how many times people access the YTV Guide page on the Site. All information gathered in this way is generic, and we do not track any individual users from this, but only calculate how many visits have taken place.

Cookie technology is used on our Site to maximize the Site experience. For example, we use cookies to keep track of a user's time zone information which allows us to customize our schedule and give accurate show times. We also use cookies to keep track of a user's progress through a game we may have on our Site. No personal information is gathered from these cookies.

When a user sends an email message to YTV through the website, two pieces of information are automatically stamped on the message. These are the time that the message was sent, and the IP address it was sent from. This is a precautionary measure against any potentially threatening messages being sent to YTV, its staff, or the public. This information is only used in those extreme cases where we feel someone's safety may be at risk.

YTV.com is a Site for kids. Therefore, there are certain laws that we are required to follow. One of the rules is that users under the age of 16 require parental consent prior to providing any personal information. However, there are other important privacy measures we take such as never asking for more personal info than what we deem necessary - and storing any info we do collect in a secure database only accessible by the YTV.com staff. We take extra steps to prevent members from disclosing their personal info on our Site by monitoring the interactive features and actively enforcing our rules.

Any personal identifiable info collected from our members is for YTV.com purposes only (e.g. Membership verification, contest fulfillment, etc.) We will never sell or give any of this information to third parties. Sometimes we may share aggregated info collected from our Polls, however specific Members are never identified.

Please keep in mind that this Privacy Policy applies to YTV.com only. Occasionally, we may have links to other Sites, including those of sponsors and partners. And although we do our best to ensure that these third parties share our views about privacy protection and safety, we don't have control over how they collect and use personal information from visitors. That's why always a good idea to check out a Site's privacy policy - even if you've linked to it from YTV.com.

We review this policy regularly and will update it (and other sections of our website) whenever necessary. If there are ever changes made to the way we collect or use personal information, we will always inform our Members.

With YTV.com Membership, users will have the option to receive email Newsletters from YTV.com. The Newsletter will be sent out periodically and provide program updates, information on special events, new contests, and YTV host messages. This Newsletter can be cancelled at any time by following the simple steps outlined at the bottom of the Newsletter.

The web is a great place to hang out, to find out stuff, and to share comments and ideas with people who are into the same kind of stuff you are.

But the net isn't always a safe place - so we've put together some tips for you to read that will help you handle situations if they come up.

First thing is don't give out personal information without asking your parents. Personal information can mean:

Your name 

Your address 

Your phone number 

Your mom or dad's name 

The name of your school 

Your teacher or your friend's names 

Secondly, if you run into something on the internet that makes you uncomfortable - whether it's on the web or it's sent to you - tell your mom or dad, or an adult you can talk to, and get them to deal with it. Never agree to meet anyone you have "met" online.

Never send your picture over the internet without checking with your parents or another adult. Don't answer mean messages, or rude ones, or messages asking for personal information. If you do get a message like that - tell your parents right away, so they can help you deal with it. Make sure you obey the rules that your parents have set out for you. Make up a cool nickname for when you join a chat or a game online. Never tell anyone your real name or your password. Get your parents to read the safety for parent's tips.

The web is a great place for kids to hang out and learn about topics that are of interest to them. However, there are areas on the internet that are not appropriate for children.

The guidelines we have drawn up are a starting point for parents of children who surf. The most important thing is to be aware of what your children are doing online. This may mean surfing with your children, or talking to them about the Sites that they like or that they have recently discovered on the web.

Make surfing a family activity, particularly with young children.

Set ground rules, so each person knows what is expected of them. For example, you could go through the safety tips together so everyone understands the whats and the whys.

There are software programs that allow parents to block certain websites from their kids. Some programs are more flexible than others, so you may want to shop around to find one that you're comfortable with.

Any questions, comments or requests concerning the YTV Privacy Policy can be directed to G.Remy, Privacy Officer at interactive@corusent.com.
